import {FAQItem} from "../components/FAQ";

export const pitFAQ: FAQItem[] = [
    {
        question: "Are gifts and tips profits?",
        answer: "you betcha",
        isDefault: true,
        value: "question-one"
    },
    {
        question: "Am I self employed?",
        answer: "yes if , no if",
        value: "question-two"
    },
    {
        question: "When do I have to pay?",
        answer: "some time",
        value: "question-three"
    },
    {
        question: "Can I pay for previous tax year?",
        answer: "yes, and here's why...",
        value: "question-four"
    },
    {
        question: "What if this...?",
        answer: "yes or no, and here's why...",
        value: "question-five"
    },
    {
        question: "Amazon wishlist taxable? ",
        answer: "yes or no, and here's why...",
        value: "question-six"
    },
]
export const cteFAQ: FAQItem[] = [
    {
        question: "Do I get a tax refund if working from home?",
        answer: "electricities etc..",
        isDefault: true,
        value: "question-one"
    },
    {
        question: "How can I prove that certain item is for business?",
        answer: "yes if , no if",
        value: "question-two"
    },
    {
        question: "Can I get a refund on travel expenses?",
        answer: "some time",
        value: "question-three"
    },
    {
        question: "I haven't paid tax for a while, what should I do?",
        answer: "yes, and here's why...",
        value: "question-four"
    },
    {
        question: "What if this...?",
        answer: "yes or no, and here's why...",
        value: "question-five"
    },
    {
        question: "Other questions",
        answer: "yes or no, and here's why...",
        value: "question-six"
    },
]